A Guide to the Papers of the Tucker, Harrison and Smith Families, 1790-1940
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- "Natural Philosophy" notes from University of Virginia of F. H. Smith 1851, 1 item (Box 51)
- Appointment of F. H. Smith as Assistant in School of Mathematics 1851 Oct. 23, 1 item (Box 51)
- E. B. Smith's Catalogue of Minerals at University of Virginia 1853, 1 item (Box 51)
- "Natural Philosophy" Notes - University of Virginia 1856, 1 item (Box 51)
- "Chemistry" Notes - University of Virginia 1857, 1 item (Box 52)
- Notebook of Ancient History 1857, 1 item (Box 52)
- Astronomical Data of Professor Francis H. Smith, University of Virginia 1869, ca. 10 items (Box 52)
- Notes on the Spectoscope, University of Virginia 1870, 5 items (Box 52)
- List of Scientific Books owned by F. H. Smith 1870, 1 item (Box 52)
- Program - Athletic Events - University of Virginia 1870, 1 item (Box 52)
- Notebooks 1870, 2 items (Box 52)
- Tribute to William B. Rogers 1870, 1 item (Box 52)
- Quarterly reports of Eliza L. C. Smith 1871 Dec. 12, 2 items (Box 52)
- Broadside: Moral and Religious Status of University of Virginia 1876, 1 item (Box 52)
- Gessner Harrison Smith - Progress Reports - University of Virginia 1876-1881, 12 items (Box 52)
- Broadside - University of Virginia "Her Aim and Destiny" 1877, 1 item (Box 52)
- Diplomas from locust Dale and University of Virginia 1877-1879, 11 items (Box 52)
- Exam, Junior Latin, University of Virginia 1878, 1 item (Box 52)
- Public Day Exercises, Programme, University of Virginia 1878, 2 items (Box 52)
- Testimonials for C. W. Kent 1882 May, 8 items (Box 52)
- Resolution re: Water Works 1884, 1 item (Box 52)
- Public Exercises: University of Virginia 1886, 1 item (Box 52)
- Ledger containing grades 1892-1893, 1 item (Box 52)
- Poetry notes 1893-1897, ca. 5 items (Box 53)
- Papers of C. W. Kent re: YMCA, Library Committee, etc. ca. 1895-1915, ca. 30 items (Box 53)
- Lecture notes on Tennyson, C. W. Kent 1896-1897, 1 item (Box 53)
- Broadside: M. A. Latin - University of Virginia 1900, 1 item (Box 53)
- Application Form to University of Virginia, with handwritten notes 1901-1902, 1 item (Box 53)
- Charles W. Kent's addresses, notes, miscellaneous papers 1903-1912, ca. 60 items (Box 53)
- Notes and notebooks 1905, 6 items (Box 53)
- Shakespeare notebook 1905, 1 item (Box 53)
- Physics Exams and Grade Sheet 1906-1907, 4 items (Box 53)
- List of Natural Philosophy Students 1907 June 5, 1 item (Box 53)
- Lectures and Addresses 1911, 2 items (Box 53)
- Obituary of Mrs. William Barton Rogers 1911 May 19, 1 item (Box 54)
- Lecture notes and addresses of Charles Kent 1915-1917, ca. 85 items (Box 54)
- Class Roll and Grade Book - English B - University of Virginia 1916, 1 item (Box 54)
- Program for University - Lewis-Clark Statue 1919, 1 item (Box 54)
- Program - Unveiling of George Rogers Clark Monument 1921, ALS (Box 54)
- List of books to read for course of Reading on History and Biography n. d., 1 item (Box 54)
- Medical Notes n. d., 3 items (Box 54)
- George M. Peek - Physical Laboratory Records n. d., 1 item (Box 54)
- Plant drawings of Eleanor Douglas Kent n. d., ca. 15 items (Box 54)
- 2 Plates - Glass Reflections from Mercury n. d., 2 items (Box 54)
- Notes re: University of Virginia n. d., 1 item (Box 54)
- Report to Board of Visitors n. d., ALS (Box 54)
- Report of Faculty Committee re: Student Faculty Relations n. d., 1 item (Box 54)
- Resolution offered by Josiah Ryland, Jr. n. d., 1 item (Box 54)
- Resolution re: Chaplaincy n. d., 1 item (Box 54)
- Printed Table of Latin Prepositions by Dr. Gessner Harrison n. d., 1 item (Box 54)
- Miscellaneous notes n. d., ca. 10 items (Box 54)
- Copy of an act concerning Public Contracts 1808 April 20, 1 item (Box 54)
- Survey Plat - of Lands, General Alexander Brown 1845, 1 item (Box 54)
- Memorandum concerning the claim to the Church Property at Leesburg 1847 May 3, 1 item (Box 54)
- Dr. Peachey Harrison - Note as member of Board of Trustees of Methodist Church, Harrisonburg 1848 March 4, 1 item (Box 54)
- Directions for Francis and Edward Smith 1852 Aug., 2 items (Box 54)
- Appointment of Summerfield Smith as snd Lt. Engineers 1862 June 24, 1 item (Box 54)
- "At home" Notice of Mrs. C. Bently 1868 Feb. 26, 1 item (Box 54)
- Tableau at Calvary Chapel, Augusta 1871 Aug., 1 item (Box 54)
- Miscellaneous announcements 1876-1894, 4 items (Box 54)
- Martin Luther Concert 1883, 1 item (Box 54)
- Mary Stuart's list of those present at party on Yacht at Cobb's Island 1890 July 10-17, 1 item (Box 54)
- Columbian Concert 1893-1894, 2 items (Box 54)
- Program Jamestown Exposition 1907, 1 item (Box 55)
- Plat of lots near Frys Springs belonging to C. W. Kent 1914 April, 1 item (Box 55)
- Applications for Home for Aged 1916-1917, 4 items (Box 55)
- Minutes adopted by Vestry of Church of St. Matthew and St. Timothy in Memory of Robert Lewis Harrison 1932 Oct. 17, 1 item (Box 55)
- Circulate to Dr. Peachey Harrison n. d., 1 item (Box 55)
- Hymn copied by Maria F. (Tucker) Rives with note by her sister, Mary Lelia Tucker n. d., 1 item (Box 55)
- Ladies Auxiliary Suggestions n. d., 1 item (Box 55)
- Old Blanford Church n. d., 1 item (Box 55)
- Postcards n. d., 7 items (Box 55)
- Prayer of Daniel G. Smith n. d., 1 item (Box 55)
- Recipe: Casey's Composition n. d., 1 item (Box 55)
- Religious Papers of Edward Tiffin Harrison n. d., 21 items (Box 55)
- Photograph of Tucker and Duncan [Smith?] taken in New York ca. 1899, 1 item (Box 55)
- Unidentified Photographs n. d., 5 items (Box 55)
- Miscellaneous announcements 1846-1892, 8 items (Box 55)
- Miscellaneous Papers 1849- ca. 1900, 6 items (Box 55)
- Miscellaneous Fragments ca. 1850, 2 items (Box 55)
- Miscellaneous Papers 1910-1915, 3 items (Box 55)
- Papers of Dr. Peachey Harrison n. d., 3 items (Box 55)
- Miscellaneous Papers of Eliza L. C. Smith n. d., 10 items (Box 55)
- Miscellaneous Papers n. d., 6 items (Box 55)
- Miscellaneous Papers n. d., 5 items (Box 55)
- Miscellaneous Printed Matter ca. 1870-1900, ca. 25 items (Box 55)
- Printed Matter - University of Virginia ca. 1875-1930, ca. 34 items (Box 55)
- Miscellaneous Printed Matter ca. 1880-1930, ca. 5 items (Box 55)
- Richmond Dispatch 1887, 1 item (Box 55)
- Newspaper Clippings ca. 1890-1911, ca. 20 items (Box 55)
- Newspaper article on W. Wilson ca. 1914, 1 item (Box 55)
- Civil War Diary 1861-1862, ALS (Box 56)
- Diary, probably by Edward H. De. Jarnette 1877-1878 (Box 56)
- Record of Expenses and Journal of Gessner Harrison Smith 1882 (Box 56)
- Ledger of Charles W. Kent 1891-1937 (Box 56)
- Mary Stuart Smith's Memoirs of Gessner Harrison Smith (1861-1892) n. d. (Box 56)
- Copy book - "A Few Notes from Robert Louis Stevenson in the Pacific" n. d. (Box 56)
- Compass, Protractor, Scale and Dissecting Kit (Box 56)